To be continued
Good morning
Thank you
I'm going to explain the plan, but I'm
going to explain it.
Today, I'm going to ask your parents to
do a little questionnaire.
I took it.
I want you to put on a mosaic.
I asked you to take 16 questions.
I'm sure I should tell you this.
No!
I've made a quiz.
First, I'll tell you what I asked my
parents.
I'll read one of the three parents.
Please guess who the parent is.
I don't know what I asked.
If my parents give me a question, I'll
be covered in seaweed.
I can't give up.
Don't look at me.
I thought you were going to look at me.
I'm going to explain the first
question.
I'll tell you what I like about my
daughter.
I'm embarrassed.
I think it's a bad idea to read it with
emotions.
I'll read it in a loud voice.
I'm embarrassed. I'm shy.
Please forgive me.
Thank you for being my daughter.
Who is it?
All of them.
The answer is one of the three.
It's Ayako Tonodama.
It depends on who wrote it.
Maybe my mom.
But my mom is not shy.
What?
My dad.
I'm not shy.
I'm a girl.
I'm a girl who does a lot of things.
I'm a girl who wears afro at a wedding.
I've decided.
Please read the question.
Rime's mom.
Rune.
The answer is Rime.
I'm embarrassed.
Is it your dad?
I like everything about you.
Don't go home.
I'm moved.
I'm watching you.
Don't write good things at this time.
I like everything about you.
The second question.
Tell me your daughter's childhood
habits.
I don't have any.
There are three answers.
1. Standing on a papaya or a bed.
2. Dancing at a supermarket or a
convenience store.
3. Ranking everything.
I don't have the desire to rank
anything.
No.
Do you?
Let's go with this.
RUN-chan!
YUNA!
Thank you for watching!
I think it's a little different.
The correct answer is Mitsuki.
What?
Were you walking while dancing?
I think so.
I was walking on a roller skate.
I remember that.
Did you wear a shoe lace?
Yes.
I thought it was a shoe lace.
I like to slip and hit people.
You are a mischievous girl.
The third question.
What is the most angry thing you have
ever done to your daughter?
The answer is that I don't remember
what I was angry about.
Why?
I don't remember.
I don't remember at all.
I remember the most angry thing I've
ever done.
Are you ready?
Please answer.
Rina
Rin-chan
The answer is
Nishiki-san
Ah
See?
Which one is the best?
I don't remember the other one
Then, the next question
Q. What did you do when your daughter
got angry at you?
Eh?
The answer is
Q. If you put a small box of chocolate
in the room,
Q. the number of people who can't come
will increase, so don't meet anymore
Ah
Don't say it
I
I'm the best
You are the best
Ah
I'm angry
What is this?
I have a seat for the person in charge,
but I have to take a ticket in public
I might get hit by someone else, but
I said it about 5 times
Then, the fifth question
Q. What color do you think your
daughter is if she is not a member color
now?
Eh?
Q. Please tell me the reason
Yes
The answer is
Q. Blue
Q. She used to look good in blue
clothes when she was a child
Eh?
Isn't it Yuna?
Ah
It's different
It's true, it's Rie
It's Rie in the elimination method
It's Rie
The correct answer is
Q. Black
I like black
She looked good in blue clothes
It's a good match
That's right
It will be purple
The sixth question
Q. Please tell me the death candidate
of the current game name
Q. Izumi Pink
Ah
Why?
Q. There is a reason for this
Q. When she entered this world, she was
told that her name was not Izumi Pink,
and her family believed it
Who?
Ah
It's so funny
I know
Ah
Let's say it together
One, two
Rie
Izumi Pink
It's so funny
I just understood
I was really going to do it
I want to be Izumi Pink
I'm serious
I'm laughing, but I'm serious
You have a good sense
I gave up
How adorable
Please subscribe to my channel!
Yay!!!
In the studio, les Chibagakubaku
b o
du
Boo Boo
Ninen
such as
each other
.
I would like you to consider again
Please tell me the reason why you want
to get married.
I've never heard of it.
I have.
I have a good reason.
The answer is to protect your
daughter's smile.
That's great.
That's too great.
Great and tolerant person.
A person who can't change even to his
parents.
A person who can change anything loose
with the power of love.
That's great.
Did you answer three questions?
I answered three questions.
I understood.
I'll start with YUNA.
RUN-CHAN
That's right.
That's great.
A person who can't change even to his
parents.
A person who can't change anything
loose with the power of love.
That's great.
Question 9.
Please tell me the first impression
when your daughter was born.
YUNA is a girl.
But YUNA is a boy.
But YUNA is the first child.
I think YUNA is a girl.
I'll tell you my impression.
YUNA is a boy.
RINNE
The answer is RUN-CHAN.
That's great.
I thought RINNE was a girl.
I thought RINNE was a boy.
Is that so?
That's why RINNE is a girl.
I didn't think so.
Question 10.
Please tell me the impressive episode
when you were a child.
The answer is
When I went to buy a nanoseal, I
recommended a red one.
But I was told that I didn't want to
buy it.
I said, If you want a red one so much,
you should buy it.
I said, I'm sure this is good.
That's great.
I don't want to buy a cat-shaped one.
But it's easy to understand.
I got it.
The answer is RUN-CHAN.
RUN-CHAN is a cat-shaped one.
I can't recommend it.
I thought it was good to buy a red one.
Question 11.
What is the correct answer if you give
a cat-shaped coffee to your daughter?
That's interesting.
I'll give you a hint.
What is it?
The answer is
Pon pon pan pan, robo pan pan.
What?
I got it.
That's great.
I'm sure it's YUNA.
I'll give you a hint.
What is the correct answer?
The answer is
PANZUKI.
It's POKU PANPAN.
That's too random.
POKU PANPAN, POKU PANPAN.
I like KOTAKU.
Question 12.
What are the hidden special skills of
KOTONE?
There are two.
The first one is eating chicken wings.
The second one is saying what she ate
on Saturday.
I can't answer that.
I got it.
I got it by the wings.
RUN-CHAN.
I also think RUN-CHAN.
RUN-CHAN?
That's correct.
She eats cleanly.
Can you say what you ate on Wednesday?
I don't know what special skill is.
I ate an apple.
She doesn't say anything.
I'll check it again.
Q. Please tell me what you were happy
to have your daughter.
Cooking
Cooking?
Rine.
That's all?
Rine's parents are funny.
You don't answer.
Rui's answer is correct.
I think so.
I can understand.
The way of writing is different.
Rui's writing is long and Rui's writing
is short.
It's written in words.
Please subscribe to this channel.
I'm
not
sure.
I don't know.
I'm
not
sure.
I'm
not
sure.
I'm not sure.
Let's talk about the second question.
Please tell us if you have something
impressive
about the present from your daughter.
This is a letter I got from the nursery
school.
I think everyone is raising their
hands.
I think this is like RINNE.
I think so, too.
Is it RINNE?
The answer is Ritsuki.
What? Maybe it's a language teacher.
I'm not sure.
I asked one more question.
Do you have any secret to your
daughter? If so, please tell us.
I think there are many secrets.
The answer is,
I have a dress that doesn't fit her,
so I put it in a closet where she
doesn't see it.
What does that mean?
For example, I hid the dress that Rine
is wearing because I thought it wasn't
cute.
Rine doesn't see it.
I'm scared.
I put a hot wire on her crotch, so I
don't think she threw it away.
I see.
I think I know the answer.
Rune.
The answer is,
I have a dress that doesn't fit her,
Kitana.
Rine, you lost one of your clothes.
I don't like to wear clothes that don't
fit me.
You don't remember which clothes you
lost?
It's funny.
You are hiding it so that I can't wear
it.
You are hiding it.
You are hiding it so that I can't wear
it.
I thought you would get angry.
I'm sorry.
That's all for today.
You probably don't remember which
clothes you lost.
Please subscribe to our channel.
We will see how you guys react to this.
How we react?
It was fun.
We all wanted to do this.
I thought we would get bad comments.
I was so moved at the beginning.
I agree.
We haven't read the comments yet.
We will see.
That's all for today.
Thank you for watching.
We will be more supportive of our
parents.
Please take care of your parents and
children.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.